Guide to the People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals (PETA) Research Files
People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals (PETA) Research Files
- Anti-Animal Organizations, 11.5 linear feet
  - National Wildlife Federation (along with items 1 through 3: 10” of information) - 5 of 5 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - National Wildlife Refuge Association (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - National Wildlife Refuge System (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - National Zoological Foundation - missing file (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Nebraska Beef Industry Development Board (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Nevada Ratite Association (promotion of emu, ostrich, and rhea farms) (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - New Jersey Milk Association (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - New Mexico Cattle Grower’s Association (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - New Mexico Livestock Board (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - New Mexico Racing Commission (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - New York Bowhunters Association (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - New York Racing Association (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - New York State Department of Environmental Conservation (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - New York Zoological Society (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - North American Equine Ranching Information Council (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - North American Fur Producers Marketing, Inc. (clothing) (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - North American Sports Network (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - North Atlantic Salmon Conservation Organization (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - North Carolina Pork Council (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Northeastern Lumber Manufacturers Association (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Northstar Policy Association (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Northwesterners for More Fish (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Ohio Poultry Association (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Oklahoma Wildlife Federation (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Omaha Steaks International (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Ontario Farm Animal Council (OFAC) (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Ontario Trappers Association (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Oregon Lands Coalition (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Oregon State Fur Breeders Association (clothing) (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Ostrich Breeders of America (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Outdoor Industry Conservation Alliance (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Outdoor Writers Association of America (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Oxfam (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Pacific Egg and Poultry Association (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Pacific Marine Fisheries Commission (PMFC) (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Parity Foundation (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Parrot Breeders Association of Virginia (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Pennsylvania Farmer’s Association (PFA) (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Pennsylvanians for the Responsible Use of Animals (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Pentagon (correspondence re: sound, etc.) (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - People and Animals Coalition of Texas (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - People Before Animals (PBA) (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - People of the West (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Perceptions Press, Inc. (objective analysis of the animal rights movement) (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Pet Industry Joint Advisory Council (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Pheasants Forever (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Piedmontese Association of the United States (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Police (LA, police corruption) (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Pork Industry Group (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Pork Producers Association (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Professional Bowhunters Society (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Professional Rodeo Cowboys Association (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Putting People First—Articles by PPF—Outdoor News (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Putting People First—Articles from Fur Age Weekly. (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Putting People First—Articles—Not by PPF - 1 of 4 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Putting People First—Articles—Not by PPF - 2 of 4 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Putting People First—Articles—Not by PPF - 3 of 4 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Putting People First—Articles—Not by PPF - 4 of 4 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Putting People First—Elizabeth Quinn (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Putting People First—Letters to the Editor by PPF. (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Putting People First—Letters to the Editor—Not by PPF (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Putting People First—Local Chapters (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Putting People First—Mailings - 1 of 4 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Putting People First—Mailings - 2 of 4 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Putting People First—Mailings - 3 of 4 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Putting People First—Mailings - 4 of 4 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Putting People First—Miscellaneous (total PPF files 6”) (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Putting People First—Miscellaneous 2” (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Putting People First—Newsletters - 1 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Putting People First—Newsletters - 2 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Quail Unlimited (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - RAFI-USA (Poultry Growers News) (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Responsible Dog Owners Association of New York (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Responsible Use of Animals Coalition (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Retail Fur Council of Canada (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Rhode Island Fur Council (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Rockville Chamber of Commerce (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Rocky Mountain Elk Foundation (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Royal Agricultural Society of England (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Ruffed Grouse Society (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Safari Club International 1” (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Salvation Army (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - San Francisco Zoological Society (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Science and Environmental Policy Project (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Seabrook Nuclear Power Plant (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Share the Earth Association (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Shriners (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Sierra Foothills Dog and Cat Owners Alliance (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Smithsonian Institution (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Snail Club of America (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Society for Animal Welfare Administrators (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Southeastern Poultry and Egg Association (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Southwest Dairy Farmers (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Sport Fishing Institute (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Sports Afield (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Sportsmen Against Hunger (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Sportsmen Conservationists of Texas (SCOT) (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Sportsmen Protecting Outdoor Recreation Traditions (S.P.O.R.T.) (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Stans Foundation (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - State Department of Agriculture (some correspondence with PETA; publicity, political appointments). (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - State Fish and Games Commission (2”; correspondence, circulars, articles, clippings) - 1 of 4 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - State Fish and Games Commission (2”; correspondence, circulars, articles, clippings) - 2 of 4 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - State Fish and Games Commission (2”; correspondence, circulars, articles, clippings) - 3 of 4 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - State Fish and Games Commission (2”; correspondence, circulars, articles, clippings) - 4 of 4 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Tennessee Farm Bureau (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Tennessee Walking Horse Breeders Association (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Texas Cattle Feeders Association (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Texas Wildlife Association (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - The Ayn Rand Institute (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - The Manzanar Project (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - The Security Advisor (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Tri-State Sportsmen Against Hunger (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Trout Unlimited (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Unified Sportsmen of Pennsylvania (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - United Bowhunters of New Jersey (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - United Conservation Alliance (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - United Dairy Industry Association (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - United Dairymen of Arizona (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - United Egg Producers (correspondence, defense of the organization) (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - United Gamefowl Breeder Association (cockfighting) (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - United Kennel Club (UKC) (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - United Meat Export Federation (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - United Nations (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - United States Agency for International Development (USAID) (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - United States Commission on Civil Rights (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA) Annual Reports of Research Facilities (2” (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)—Articles 7” - 1 of 15 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)—Articles 7” - 2 of 15 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)—Articles 7” - 3 of 15 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)—Articles 7” - 4 of 15 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)—Articles 7” - 5 of 15 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)—Articles 7” - 6 of 15 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)—Articles 7” - 7 of 15 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)—Articles 7” - 8 of 15 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)—Articles 7” - 9 of 15 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)—Articles 7” - 10 of 15 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)—Articles 7” - 11 of 15 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)—Articles 7” - 12 of 15 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)—Articles 7” - 13 of 15 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)—Articles 7” - 14 of 15 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)—Articles 7” - 15 of 15 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)—Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)—General/Miscellaneous 1” (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)—Inspection Reports - 1 of 3 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)—Inspection Reports - 2 of 3 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)—Inspection Reports - 3 of 3 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)—Lists - 1 of 8 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)—Lists - 2 of 8 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)—Lists - 3 of 8 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)—Lists - 4 of 8 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)—Lists - 5 of 8 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)—Lists - 6 of 8 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)—Lists - 7 of 8 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)—Lists - 8 of 8 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)—News Releases - 1 of 4 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)—News Releases - 2 of 4 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)—News Releases - 3 of 4 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)—News Releases - 4 of 4 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - United States Department of Agriculture (USDA)—Pamphlets (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - United States Department of Commerce (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - United States Department of Justice (government statements about animal rights extremists and activities: report from the Department of Justice in 1993.) (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - United States Department of the Interior - 1 of 5 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - United States Department of the Interior - 2 of 5 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - United States Department of the Interior - 3 of 5 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - United States Department of the Interior - 4 of 5 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - United States Department of the Interior - 5 of 5 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - United States Department of the State (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - United States Fish and Wildlife Service ( mostly about problems of enforcement, inaction, and lack of support for the ARN) - 1 of 2 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - United States Fish and Wildlife Service ( mostly about problems of enforcement, inaction, and lack of support for the ARN) - 2 of 2 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - United States Forest Service (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - United States Hide, Skin and Leather Association (USHS and LA) (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - United States Marine Corps (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - United States Park Service (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - United States Postal Service (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - United States Tuna Foundation (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - United Way (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Agribusiness Council (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Cooperative Extension Service (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Hunters Who Care (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Marine Products Board (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Poultry Federation (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Waterfowl Limited (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Western Pennsylvania Conservancy (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Western States Meat Association (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - WFLZ-FM (dropping a live turkey stuffed with case out of an airplane!!) (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Whitetail, Inc. (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Whitetails Unlimited (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Wilderness Society (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Wildlife Conservation Fund of America (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Wildlife Conservation Society (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Wildlife Forever (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Wildlife Legislative Fund of America (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Wildlife Management Institute (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Wildlife Society (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Wisconsin Agri-Business Council, Inc. (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Wisconsin Agri-View (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Wisconsin Alliance for Resources and the Environment (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Wisconsin Veal Growers Association (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Wisconsin Wildlife Federation (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Wise Use Movement (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Women Hunters and Outdoor Women (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Women Hunters of America (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Woodstream Corporation (Manufacturer of traps) (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - World Bank (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - World Bowhunters (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - World Trade Organization (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Yankee Shepherd (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Zimmer Club (trapping, hunting, etc., for teens) (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Zoovival (Box 23, Folder 39)
- Pro-Animal Organizations, 31 linear feet
  - Action 81 Inc.: Voice of the Missing - 1 of 8 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Action 81 Inc.: Voice of the Missing - 2 of 8 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Action 81 Inc.: Voice of the Missing - 3 of 8 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Action 81 Inc.: Voice of the Missing - 4 of 8 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Action 81 Inc.: Voice of the Missing - 5 of 8 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Action 81 Inc.: Voice of the Missing - 6 of 8 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Action 81 Inc.: Voice of the Missing - 7 of 8 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Action 81 Inc.: Voice of the Missing - 8 of 8 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Actors and Others for Animals (CA) (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Adebo (sanctuary) (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Adopt a Ferrett (AZ) (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Adopt-A-Greyhound (AZ) (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - African Wildlife Foundation (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Alaska Equine Rescue (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Alaska Raptor Rehabilitation Center (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Alaska Wildlife Alliance (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Alternatives to Animals (CA) (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - American Association for Science and Public Policy (AASPP) (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - American Bat Conservation Society (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - American Cetacean Society (CA) (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - American Fancy Rat and Mouse Association (AFRMA) (CA) (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - American Ferret Association (MD) (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - American Horse Protection Association, Inc. (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - American Mustang and Burro Association, Inc. (CA) (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - American Natural Hygiene Society (FL) (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - American Tortoise Rescue (CA) (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Andora: Associació Per a la Protecció d’Animals Plantes i Medi Ambient (APAPMA) (Andora) (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Animal Care Foundation (Michigan) (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Animal League Defense Fund (CA) (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Animal League Defense Fund (CA) (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Animal Media Project (CA) (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Animal Place (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Animal Protection Institute (CA) 1 of 3 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Animal Protection Institute (CA) 2 of 3 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Animal Protection Institute (CA) 3 of 3 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Animal Survival Fund (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Animal Welfare Institute (whales, birds; fur trade; correspondence with Alex Pacheco, 1979) 1 of 2 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Animal Welfare Institute (whales, birds; fur trade; correspondence with Alex Pacheco, 1979) 2 of 2 (Box 26.1, Folder 1)
  - Animaletters (FL) (Box 26.1, Folder 2)
  - Arashiyama W. Primate Center (Box 26.1, Folder 3)
  - Argentina: Miscellaneous (Argentina) (Box 26.1, Folder 4)
  - Ark Trust, Inc. (CA) (Box 26.1, Folder 5)
  - Asociación, La, Venezolana de Prevención de la Crueldad (AVEPREC) (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Associated Humane Societies (New Jersey) (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Association of Veterinarians For Animal Rights (AVAR) (CA) (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Attorneys for Animal Rights (AFAR: Animal League Defense Fund) (CA) (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Attorneys for Animals (MI) (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Audubon Zoo Wild Bird Rehabilitation Center (Louisiana) (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Australia: Animal Liberation (Australia) (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Australia: Animal Rights Advocates (Australia) (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Australia: Australian Association Against Painful Experiments on Animals (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Australia: Australian Association for Humane Research (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Australia: Australian Association for Humane Research (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Australia: Australian Association for Humane Research (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Australia: Australians for Animals (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Australia: Coalition against Duck Shooting (Australia) (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Australia: Coalition against Fur (Australia) (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Australia: Direct Action for Animal Rights (Australia) (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Australia: Free the Battery Hen Association (Australia) (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Australia: International Action against the LD-50 Test (Australia) (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Australia: Miscellaneous (Australia) (Australian Wildlife Protection Council, articles, etc.) (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Australia: Miscellaneous (Australia) (Australian Wildlife Protection Council, articles, etc.) (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Australia: Miscellaneous (Australia) (Australian Wildlife Protection Council, articles, etc.) (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Australia: People Against Vivisection (Australia) (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Australia: Vegan Society (Australia) (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Australia: Wildwatch (Australia) (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Bandon’s Free Flight Bird and Marine Mammal Rehabilitation Center (Oregon) (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Bandre’s Sea Turtle Preservation Society (FL) (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Belgium: Belgian Bird Protection Association (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Belgium: Eurogroup for Animal Welfare (Belgium) (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Belgium: Miscellaneous—Belgium (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Belgium: Suppression des Expériences sur lAnimal Vivant (Belgium) - 1 of 2 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Belgium: Suppression des Expériences sur lAnimal Vivant (Belgium) - 2 of 2 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Best Friends Animal Sanctuary (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Beyond Beef Coalition (DC) (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Beyond Pesticides (formerly known as the National Coalition against the Misuse of Pesticides, or NCAMP) - empty folder (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Black Beauty Ranch (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Blue Mountain Center of Meditation (Hasti Newletter) (CA) (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Brazil: Liga de Proveno and Crueldade Contra o Animal (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Brazil: Miscellaneous—Brazil (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Brighter Days Horse Refuge (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Bring Epidemiological Studies to Breast Cancer (BREST) (CA) (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - British Union for the Abolition of Vivisection (BUAV)—Miscellaneous - 1 of 22 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - British Union for the Abolition of Vivisection (BUAV)—Miscellaneous - 2 of 22 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - British Union for the Abolition of Vivisection (BUAV)—Miscellaneous - 3 of 22 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - British Union for the Abolition of Vivisection (BUAV)—Miscellaneous - 4 of 22 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - British Union for the Abolition of Vivisection (BUAV)—Miscellaneous - 5 of 22 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - British Union for the Abolition of Vivisection (BUAV)—Miscellaneous - 6 of 22 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - British Union for the Abolition of Vivisection (BUAV)—Miscellaneous - 7 of 22 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - British Union for the Abolition of Vivisection (BUAV)—Miscellaneous - 8 of 22 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - British Union for the Abolition of Vivisection (BUAV)—Miscellaneous - 9 of 22 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - British Union for the Abolition of Vivisection (BUAV)—Miscellaneous - 10 of 22 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - British Union for the Abolition of Vivisection (BUAV)—Miscellaneous - 11 of 22 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - British Union for the Abolition of Vivisection (BUAV)—Miscellaneous - 12 of 22 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - British Union for the Abolition of Vivisection (BUAV)—Miscellaneous - 13 of 22 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - British Union for the Abolition of Vivisection (BUAV)—Miscellaneous - 14 of 22 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - British Union for the Abolition of Vivisection (BUAV)—Miscellaneous - 15 of 22 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - British Union for the Abolition of Vivisection (BUAV)—Miscellaneous - 16 of 22 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - British Union for the Abolition of Vivisection (BUAV)—Miscellaneous - 17 of 22 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - British Union for the Abolition of Vivisection (BUAV)—Miscellaneous - 18 of 22 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - British Union for the Abolition of Vivisection (BUAV)—Miscellaneous - 19 of 22 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - British Union for the Abolition of Vivisection (BUAV)—Miscellaneous - 20 of 22 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - British Union for the Abolition of Vivisection (BUAV)—Miscellaneous - 21 of 22 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - British Union for the Abolition of Vivisection (BUAV)—Miscellaneous - 22 of 22 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Brooke Hospital for Animals, Cairo (Egypt, India, Pakistan) (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Buckfast Buttterfly Farm and Dartmoor Otter Sanctuary (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Buddhists Concerned for Animals (CA) (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Buffalo Field Campaign (Montana) (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - CA: Disabled Against Animal Research and Exploitation (DAARE) (CA) - 1 of 9 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - CA: Disabled Against Animal Research and Exploitation (DAARE) (CA) - 2 of 9 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - CA: Disabled Against Animal Research and Exploitation (DAARE) (CA) - 3 of 9 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - CA: Disabled Against Animal Research and Exploitation (DAARE) (CA) - 4 of 9 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - CA: Disabled Against Animal Research and Exploitation (DAARE) (CA) - 5 of 9 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - CA: Disabled Against Animal Research and Exploitation (DAARE) (CA) - 6 of 9 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - CA: Disabled Against Animal Research and Exploitation (DAARE) (CA) - 7 of 9 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - CA: Disabled Against Animal Research and Exploitation (DAARE) (CA) - 8 of 9 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - CA: Disabled Against Animal Research and Exploitation (DAARE) (CA) - 9 of 9 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - CA: Earth First! (CA) - 1 of 4 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - CA: Earth First! (CA) - 2 of 4 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - CA: Earth First! (CA) - 3 of 4 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - CA: Earth First! (CA) - 4 of 4 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - CA: Earth Island Institute (CA)- 1 of 3 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - CA: Earth Island Institute (CA)- 2 of 3 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - CA: Earth Island Institute (CA)- 3 of 3 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - CA: Earth Save (CA)- 1 of 2 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - CA: Earth Save (CA)- 2 of 2 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - CA: Elephant Alliance, The (CA) (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - CA: Equine Emergency Response Team (CA) (Box 32, Folder 7)